<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2777">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to Teaching Energy Literacy to Adult Learners!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/solar%20pannels.jpg" alt="" width="350" height="197" role="presentation" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_right"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purpose:
    &lt;/strong&gt;This course aims to provide adult
    educators with opportunities to increase content knowledge of energy literacy
    and principles, and to become familiar with high-quality energy literacy
    classroom materials and strategies appropriate for use with adult learners.
    Upon completion of the course, the goal is for participants to have the
    knowledge, resources, and strategies to teach energy topics across adult
    education settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;
    &lt;p style=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commitment: &lt;/strong&gt;This
        course will take approximately 3 hours to complete. You must complete all units and
        assessments to earn a certificate.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives: &lt;/strong&gt;After completing this course, you will be able to do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Define energy literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Identify the Energy Literacy Framework’s seven Essential Principles and the supporting Fundamental Concepts.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Employ strategies for teaching the seven Essential Principles to adult learners.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Use online resources to guide adult learners in exploring the seven principles and the associated concepts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This course is composed of the following:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Unit 1: Course Introduction&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Content Units:&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Unit 2: Laws of Energy (Principle 1)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Unit 3: Energy Flow (Principles 2 and 3)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Unit 4: Energy Sources and Decisions&amp;nbsp;(Principles 4 and 5)&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Unit 5: Energy Use and Society&amp;nbsp;(Principles 6 and 7)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Unit 6: Course Conclusion&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This is the main course page. Each content unit below includes a learning check activity for review and reflection, and all units include resource lists with links to websites, videos, and other materials to enhance your learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will start each unit from this page, and you will return to this page between units.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To begin, select Unit 1: Course
            Introduction below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer:
            This course has been updated for Literacy Information and Communication System
            (LINCS) under contract with the American Institutes for Research (AIR) with
            funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED), Office of Career,
            Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract No. 91990020A-0014 /
            91990022F-0346. The content and opinions expressed herein do not necessarily
            represent the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no
            official endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The
            course may contain resources by a third party outside of the Department of
            Education. As such, the Department is not responsible for its content, nor can
            it guarantee it is accessible in accordance with Section 508 of the
            Rehabilitation Act of 1973. If you need access to an accessible version, please
            reach out to the third-party vendor for assistance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence></sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1716929988</timemodified>
</section>